[Kawaii Monster]
♪ Happy, lucky, wonderful ♪
All together now!
- Make it cute!
- ♪ Happy, lucky, wonderful ♪
- Make it super cute!
- Say, cute!
- Cute!
- Yeah!
- Super cute!
- It is so cute!
Look! Cute!
So cute...
- Sorry for the wait.
- Cute!
Cute...
Kusakabe? What is it?
Huh? Are you a staff member doing cosplay?
No, it's an undercover investigation
in the name of a gap part-time job.
What? Undercover investigation?
Excuse me! Could you take a picture for us?
Sure. Go ahead.
Say cheese!
Here you go.
Well, Miss, would you like to
be in the photo with us?
That's true. She is cute.
- Come on! Let's take a photo!
- No, I'm... Well...
- Let's take a photo!
- Alright. Alright. Alright.
I'll take it. Come on.
Okay, do a cute pose!
- Cute... Wait.
- Ready, set.
So cute!
What?
I mean, why am I like this...
I want to do it! I love it!
I just can't stop loving it!
Then just do it!
I'm in 'let's do this together' mode.
I'm in 'let's make it a huge hit' mode!
I'll do it!
I'll do it too!
Are we going to do it together?
I'm going to do consulting, right?
Do it?
Do it.
Probably, I'll do it.
[Seo Design]
So, Mr. Seo, at your request,
- starting today, I will be consulting...
- No, no, no.
My request? You said you wanted to do it.
You said you wanted to do it
- while bursting into tears.
- Well...
It's liquid. Just some liquid
coming out of my eyes.
That's enough.
Anyway, we're doing this, right?
Well, though you're the one
who brought it up.
[Consultant Agreement]
This will be a formal consulting agreement.
But before that,
there's something I need to tell you.
I have no experience being passionate about
or absorbed in something.
I've never even liked a character before.
Perhaps because of that, I don't have
any sense of what 'cute' means either.
So I'm currently infiltrating various
cute-related facilities to investigate.
Like this.
I mean, you want to consult
without even understanding what cute is.
That's some nerve.
Even if I don't understand cute,
by looking at characters and goods,
I can understand the target, aim, cost rate,
and other business elements and numbers.
So you don't need to worry about that.
Or rather, I hope you can trust me on that.
I have a policy of not trusting people.
Okay, but for the sake of
- smooth business operations...
- My grandma used to say that
never trust anyone
who tells you to trust them.
- Well, she's right, but...
- Now then!
[Consulting Fee]
Impress me with your results!
What? What! What?
- What!
- Well, with this,
I'll be ordering you around
to my heart's content.
- But you don't have any work...
- And whose fault do you think that is?
I'm sorry. Let me confirm here.
I struggled with it too.
My savings are practically nothing.
But I swapped my usual big, cheap bread
- for this small, cheap bread...
- It's not enough.
- What?
Oh, but I don't know
the market rate for consulting.
But it's kind of like
a video streaming subscription, right?
For a six-month contract,
it's 30 million yen.
You're a hyena! That's hyena-ism!
That said, that figure is
for major corporations.
And there's also the matter of Takai Create.
So first, let me compensate you for that.
After that, you can pay me
based on the results.
Alright, I've also prepared a job for you.
A bakery called Oyama Bakery
[Oyama Bakery]
is commemorating its 50th anniversary.
They want an original character for the shop,
and they'd like you to design it.
Alright, though I don't really get it...
Understood. Well then, please sign here.
A written pledge?
Well, just some rules from me, too.
Common sense, got it?
Don't talk about Merry in front of me.
Don't talk about Omishima.
Don't talk about Cynical Molco.
Don't tell anyone that liquid
came out of my eyes.
If you tell them, you're fired.
And when I say fired, I mean fired.
All right. And with that,
our contract is sealed.
Mr. Seo, before I begin consulting,
I have one important question.
What is our goal?
What do you want to do?
What do you want to create?
If we are to create a new character,
I think it will also be
connected to that concept.
Please think it over carefully.
What's our goal?
Goal...
Cynical Molco is very popular, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
We are quite surprised ourselves.
How can one create such a hit product?
[Merry President, Takumi Omishima]
You just called it a hit product,
but we do not think of
our characters as products.
[This is where a new era begins]
They're more like our children.
Like our children.
This one is like a child to me.
It's okay.
Please trust me...
The same goes for Molco.
With the initial settings and designs
you came up with,
it didn't seem like they would sell well.
So I made some adjustments.
As a result, it became
an unprecedentedly huge hit.
That very ruthlessness is
what made them evolve.
And I believe that evolution
is what led to this hit.
Evolution?
- Well...
- He doesn't get it.
He doesn't get anything.
- Well, no...
- He killed it!
This guy killed it!
- Cheese! Yeah!
- Let's do a heart too.
Cute?
Molco!
Hey, that plushie will get wet. Here.
Because Molco, who's usually all "hmph,"
goes "hmph" at the very end.
Then everyone goes "hmph,"
and I go "hmph" too.
I see. "Hmph", huh?
Hey, your nose is running.
Molco.
Oh, sorry, you're studying.
No, it's fine.
I was just thinking that it's love.
Love...
Oh, no.
Oh, it's getting late.
- Aren't you sleepy? You okay?
- I'm not sleepy.
Oh, yeah, I think I'm okay.
S-S-So, how is it? The world of
creating characters as a business?
Well, it's tougher than I thought.
First, the producer or project leader
decides what kind of character to make,
and who to target.
Next, a character designer
creates the design,
and while they devise the name
and setting, the character...
Well, anyway, it's tough,
and only a handful succeed.
But basically, manga, anime, games,
they are also
character creation businesses, right?
Well, but those at least
have some predictability,
since they're already popular.
But succeeding with
a so-called mascot character,
like Hello Kitty, is quite difficult.
Oh, but isn't Cynical Molco like that too?
Well, the success of that character is
[Character Business Revolution]
thanks to this person's acumen,
[By Takumi Omishima]
or rather, his ability to sniff out a hit.
This one is like a child to me.
It's okay.
Please trust me...
Wait a minute!
Hmph, hmph, hmph.
Who are you?
- Mol...
- Molco!
- Hmph.
Hmph, hmph.
- Mol...
- Stop!
Mol...
Stop it!
Molco!
Good morning.
Hmph, hmph, hmph.
About that goal business.
Yes?
My goal is vengeance for Full Tummy Molco,
who was killed
before it ever saw the light of day!
V-e-n-g-e-a-n-c-e.
Vengeance!
Vengeance?
[Episode 2]
[Hello, Ms. Anna Kusakabe.
Need me to check anything for you?]
[What does it mean, aiming for vengeance?]
Vengeance is an illegal act in modern times.
What is this exchange?
Is it done? The vengeance plan?
Sorry, not yet.
I mean, my specialty
is management strategy support
- and operational efficiency...
- Is it done?
The vengeance plan.
I'll do my best.
[Vengeance! Chushingura]
Ms. Kusakabe?
Oh, you're from Merry.
Well... Mr. Hirose, right?
Yes.
Molco's autograph session
is happening in the back right now.
- It's Molco!
- Hello.
Here.
- Thank you.
By the way, are you still
working with Mr. Seo?
Yes. I'm officially working with him now.
I'm the consultant.
I see. That's good.
Oh, yes. Well...
I wanted to say again, I'm truly sorry
for all the trouble I caused
at the competition the other day.
It's fine. That ended up
being canceled, anyway.
Could it be that
- it was because of the mess we caused?
- No, no, not at all.
In the end, nothing really clicked,
so nobody ended up qualifying.
But is that okay?
The shopping mall is going to be built,
and it needs a character...
That's true.
So, I contacted
the organizing company a while ago,
and now among the higher-ups...
they're saying that they'd like
Mr. Seo to draw it again.
- Mr. Seo?
- Hey! Wait, wait!
♪ Se, se, se, yoi, yoi, yoi ♪
♪ Chitter-chatter, chitter-chat ♪
Excuse me.
♪ Chitter-chatter-chat ♪
Sorry for the wait.
[Vengeance Plan]
Here is the vengeance plan.
This is from the other day...
Creating a character for
the shopping mall to be built in Nerima.
The client says they want you
to draw the character again.
However, when the character is announced,
they want to prominently feature your title
as the designer of Cynical Molco.
- And we'll need Merry's permission...
- You want me to...
If you're serious about this...
you're hell-bound.
The official name of this project is...
the Shopping Mall Character Project,
Volume Two.
- It's Volume Two!
- Two?
Volume One is the character creation
for the Itabashi shopping mall,
and the creator is...
[Merry Co., Ltd.]
Merry.
If the Nerima character you create
becomes more popular than
Merry's Itabashi character...
It'd be successful vengeance!
The fee is high, and if you establish
a track record on a big project like this,
it will certainly be advantageous
for you in the future.
Even though you just broke
one of the rules around here...
[Don't talk about Merry]
I forgive you.
Just watch. I'll make Nerima defeat Itabashi.
Defeat it!
I'll make Nerima defeat Itabashi!
[Nerima Official Anime Character: Nerimaru]
♪ I was supposed to do ♪
[Itabashi Tourism Character: Rinrin]
♪ Proper consulting ♪
♪ Seeking vengeance at a shopping mall ♪
♪ I was supposed to do cute consulting ♪
♪ Vengeance, in Nerima, against Itabashi ♪
♪ An amateur girl who
doesn't know the right answer ♪
♪ An amateur girl oozing anxiety ♪
[Oyama Bakery]
Oh, hello. This is Oyama Bakery.
Thank you for your patronage.
- Hello.
Well, is it done yet? Our character?
Well... the deadline
hasn't passed yet, right?
I'm sorry. No, I was just
curious about how it's going.
Vengeance...
Vengeance.
The designer is working on it right now.
I see, I see!
[First 50 visitors get a free]
Well, it's our first time having
[original Oyama character keychain]
an original store character.
Well... I'm just really excited about it.
Can you imagine an original
character for Oyama Bakery?
That's exactly why I'd want to get one.
Well, you see,
it's our 50th anniversary coming up.
I was thinking we could give them out
to our regular customers and kids.
- Right?
- Yeah, I want one.
Understood. We'll do our best
to meet your expectations.
Excuse us.
Vengeance... Vengeance...
- Vengeance... Vengeance...
- Well, Mr. Seo?
Mr. Seo!
What? Why are you shouting all of a sudden?
The Nerima project is fine,
but what about the other job?
The bakery, right?
What, you thought I hadn't done it?
- No, it's not that...
- You surprised me.
I thought maybe you didn't trust me. Yikes.
Vengeance.
It's done.
Good morning.
I drew it. The Nerima one, I drew it.
What do you think? Is it cute? Cute, right?
Well... It's a bit different from
the image the client is looking for.
What? Different? What?
Where? Where is it different?
More importantly, the deadline for
Oyama Bakery is approaching.
- How's the progress?
- I'm...
I'm the type who doesn't want anyone
to see my work in progress.
Is that so? But I will see it.
Wait! You really don't trust me! Wait!
[Oyama Bakery]
I'm clicking now.
Is this...
Is this hijiki seaweed?
I'm really sorry.
Please give us a little more time.
No, it's fine.
Guess the designer really cares that much.
What? There isn't any Oyama Bakery keychain?
- There isn't?
No, no, no, that's not true! There is! Right?
- Look forward to it, okay?
- Yes!
Hello, this is Kusakabe from
Horai Consulting... No, I mean...
I finally drew it.
- The one for Mr. Oyama?
- I drew the Nerima one.
Want to see? I'll send it. There, I sent it.
Well... Is that thing on its head a helmet?
It's a hat. A hat.
So, what do you think?
Is it cute? Cute, right?
Well... I'll gather some more
information about Nerima.
We can incorporate that
and adjust the design a bit more.
Adjust? Why?
Why is an adjustment necessary?
Well... just to be doubly sure.
To aim for something more solid.
All right, fine.
By the way, what about Oyama Bakery?
[Seo Design]
Good morning.
I drew it. I drew it! I drew it!
Oh, great! Then I'll take it
to Mr. Oyama right away...
What do you think?
Cute, right? This is the idea.
Send it. Just send it to them.
I can't send this.
What?
Because it's Chushingura, isn't it?
It's even more Kuranosuke
than Kuranosuke Oishi himself, isn't it?
[Vengeance! Chushingura]
How and where is it Kuranosuke?
Anyway, I can't send that.
I can't just send it to them like that.
Fine, then.
Wait a minute! Wait, wait!
[Send]
I'm clicking!
[Sent]
Ah! It's done...
You sent it? Kuranosuke? You sent Kuranosuke?
With this, vengeance...
Mr. Seo? Mr. Seo? Seo...
Hey, wake up! Oyama Bakery. Oyama Bakery!
Molco...
[Sinful Chestnut]
I am truly sorry.
In three more days... No, two more days,
we'll be able to finish it.
Please.
Ms. Kusakabe.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to ask someone else.
I really want to make it in time
for our 50th anniversary.
[Oyama Bakery
has terminated the contract with us]
[Latest Video: Getting Close to the Real Face
of Merry President Takumi Omishima!]
[His Resolve as a Leader
and Passion for Merry]
This week, we'd like to ask you
about your social circle.
[Merry President, Takumi Omishima]
This is Ms. Kumi Sakoda,
[Kitchen Sakoda President, Kumi Sakoda]
the president of that hot topic right now,
[Kitchen Sakoda]
Kitchen Sakoda, isn't it?
I heard that you're very close.
That's right.
We have a mutual acquaintance
who introduced us.
She's a very powerful person.
We want to spread the charm
of Kitchen Sakoda to the world.
Why was she with Omishima...
- Welcome.
- Lunchtime, dinnertime,
enjoyable days with family and friends.
- Welcome to Hot! Hot!
- Hello, good morning.
Hey, there's something I want to ask you.
Oh, I'm in the middle of something
right now. Perhaps tomorrow?
What are you in the middle of?
It's a trade secret.
So, tomorrow, then.
There are juicy meat dishes available...
Hot! Hot!
You see, humans unconditionally
find round things cute.
I knew it.
Meeting secretly with Merry...
When you reach my level, you will know...
Is something wrong?
No, I just felt something like
murderous intent.
What?
Meeting secretly with Merry...
- What?
- Is something wrong?
The company behind the Nerima
shopping mall wants to meet.
What?
[Neri-Morusuke]
It's great, isn't it?
This edgy vibe is just brutal.
It blows right past all the rules.
It really strikes a chord!
It means...
Let's go with this for Nerima.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you.
- What do you think?
- This is the only way, right?
You said it.
I'm sorry.
I really don't understand.
What are characters, anyway?
Fired.
Huh? Neck?
[*"Fired" and "neck" sound close in Japanese]
Oh, Kuranosuke's?
Dismissal.
Dis... Dismissal?
Because I realized I can manage on my own.
Also, a consultant who doesn't
understand cute is a burden.
Above all, I can't trust you.
You're secretly connected to Omishima.
Dismissal.
Zapaan!
How do you feel? Did it wash away?
That cloudy feeling?
No, it's stuck. It's clogged in my throat!
Excuse me! A large Zapaan shochu
with sweet potato!
Another shochu, and another one of this too.
- Okay. Coming right up.
- But how did he know about
Mr. Omishima and me?
Hey, isn't it okay already?
You're fired, so that means
you're free, right?
Want to go to Yamashiroya sometime?
Do you know that place?
They have lots of cute stuff!
How about it? This Sunday?
Sunday's not great for me.
- Thank you for your patronage.
- Mr. Oyama, excuse me. I'd like to switch.
- Oh, okay. Please go ahead.
- Alright.
Vengeance.
Do you have a minute?
- Hey! Hey!
- No way!
I said, no way! I don't want to,
not even for a minute!
Understood. Then, is five hours okay?
What are you thinking?
Then six hours... Seven hours.
Why is it increasing?
- Your face is like The Shining...
- Eight hours... Nine hours... Ten hours!
Eleven...
What?
Oyama Bakery is celebrating
its 50th anniversary.
Welcome.
It's Oyama Bakery.
- We're handing out balloons.
- Can you see the poster?
[Original Oyama Character Keychain]
It's Oyama Bakery's 50th anniversary.
[Canceled]
Canceled...
Why?
I heard they looked for another designer
after that, but couldn't find one.
And the AI designs didn't click either,
so in the end...
We're having an event today. Please go ahead.
I still don't understand what is cute.
And I'm an amateur in the character business.
But I do know this.
You came! Take it!
- Come on. Take the balloon.
- What? No character keychains?
I'm sorry. It can't be helped.
- Balloons are nice too.
- We prioritized our own selfish feelings.
We didn't face Mr. Oyama properly.
And for someone,
we robbed them of a chance
to encounter a lifelong love.
It's done.
What are you drawing?
You're good! Amazing!
Good!
Sticker. Put a sticker
on your favorite bread.
Mr. Seo?
- Hey!
- Oyama Bakery is celebrating
- Mr. Seo!
- its 50th anniversary!
- We're a delicious, delicious bakery!
- Excuse me.
I'm Seo, the designer, and this time...
No, no, no... No, it's not that...
That kind of thing...
You see, there are children here.
No clue what the Oyama
character keychain looks like.
Can I borrow a pen?
- I like the bread one.
- Stop it.
- Or that...
- All kinds are good.
Can I have a balloon?
Sure.
Impressive!
So good!
Here.
It's old man Oyama! Old man bread loaf!
Awesome!
Draw one for me too! An old man hot dog.
- Great drawing!
- Next, draw me a melon bread, too!
- That's good.
- Look, look!
It really is amazing, isn't it?
Awesome!
Here you go.
- Old man!
- Old man hot dog!
Can I draw these too?
- Hold on.
- Oh, okay.
Amazing.
- Awesome.
- Amazing, amazing.
Characters really are amazing, aren't they?
They turn something ordinary
into something special.
And both the receiver
and the giver become happy.
Well...
About Mr. Omishima,
I should have told you properly.
Of course, he was just a client
from my consulting days,
but I just thought it
might be better not to mention it.
But...
that might have been
a selfish judgment on my part.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
Excuse me.
We're not done talking yet.
Well...
[Mi! Berry Good!]
So,
does that mean this character
is also no good?
Yes.
You just said it earlier.
Characters turn something ordinary
into something special,
and make both the receiver
and the giver happy.
Would you be happy to receive this?
I want to redo it.
So, you know, make that kind of contact.
- But I'm fired...
- As some people say,
once trust is lost, it takes
several times more, whatever,
to restore it, or something like that.
So...
Do... Do your best.
I'll try contacting them.
[Seo Design]
- They said okay to the redraw.
- I see.
But the client likes
the current Kuranosuke idea,
so we need to propose something
that's even better than that.
Let's see, Nerima...
Nerima...
[Revised Character Design]
We need a little more impact.
Something like a sense of incongruity.
Incongruity.
Understood. I'll revise it immediately.
I'm looking forward to it.
And regarding the character
for the Nerima shopping mall,
it seems Mr. Seo has been chosen to draw it.
Oh?
Mr. Seo?
[Specialties, Edamame, Nature, Green,
Nerima, Daikon Radish, Komatsuna, Blueberry]
I'm back.
Hello? Yes, this is Kusakabe.
I'm terribly sorry. Really, I'm truly sorry.
Cancelled?
So I'm not allowed to redraw it?
No.
It seems that the plan
to have you draw the Nerima character
has been scrapped entirely.
- Why?
- They just said that
it was a decision from above.
Hello, Fuchinobe?
There's something I want to ask you.
[Hirose]
What?
Oh, Mr. Seo? I'm glad you answered!
Actually, right now...
It's been a while, Mr. Omishima.
Yes, it has been a while.
Please, right this way.
Are you Horibe? The one working
the gap part-time job?
Well, wait...
You, of all days, late today?
- No, I'm not Horibe...
- Anyway, hurry up.
President Omishima is already here.
- What?
- Come on! Hurry!
- Come on!
[Limited-Time Cynical Molco Course]
This is amazing.
Collaborating with a restaurant like this.
Officially, it starts tomorrow,
but today is a special occasion.
Excuse me.
This is Cynical Molco.
We will be serving your meal shortly.
I think you need a bit more training.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
So hard. So hard. So hard.
Dressing up in mascot costumes is so hard.
It's okay. It's okay. It's hard.
Being here reminds me of eight years ago.
I was launching an electronics company,
and you were my consultant.
Of course, business was booming.
We made a good team, didn't we?
Never imagined I'd run into
my old partner as a rival
in the character creation business.
Rival?
But we're just a team of two people.
I'm not so foolish as
to let my guard down around you.
In that case, the rumor
might not be false, then.
Rumor?
Well, the character creation for the Nerima
shopping mall that we were in charge of
was suddenly canceled.
I've heard about that.
Of course you have.
Because Merry is the replacement.
It pains me to say this,
but it was a request from the client.
There's also one more groundless rumor.
About the character for the Itabashi
shopping mall that your company is handling,
I heard that was also
initially a competition.
But just before the second round of judging,
the competition was abruptly canceled,
- and the replacement was...
- Us, right.
Well, both were requests from the clients.
Well, it is just a rumor.
But even if it were true,
is there a problem?
No.
It's not against the law.
Excuse me.
However, as a rival in the same industry,
I do have one piece of advice.
Oh? Please, by all means.
Mr. Omishima, your way of doing things...
is killing these little children.
And in the Itabashi competition,
didn't you also kill the children
created by all those designers?
I'm sorry, my apologies.
I never imagined that
you would be influenced by Mr. Seo.
That someone like you would call
a mere product a child.
I know, right? I share the same opinion.
But
our way of thinking
isn't always the right answer.
Mr. Seo makes me realize it.
Yes?
When he's in front of something he loves,
he stops hearing other people's voices,
forgets to eat,
and loses track of day and night.
With just that, he attains a happiness
that could reach the heavens,
and if it's taken away,
he'll stake his entire life to get it back.
If a man like Mr. Seo
says that this is his child,
then maybe that's just the truth.
At least, I want to
believe in what Mr. Seo is saying.
- Is that your advice?
- No.
My advice is that I don't want you
to be overconfident, like I once was.
All right, thank you for the meal.
Goodbye, then.
Ms. Kusakabe, you seem to be half asleep.
So...
How about this?
Did that wake you up a little?
How far will you go?
Oh, you still seem to be dreaming.
So shall we have a contest? Let's see...
Seo Design, with you as the consultant,
and us, Merry,
competing to see who can create
a new star character first.
Let's gather the media
and make it a flashy event.
Of course, the loser will have to
withdraw from this industry.
What do you say?
We'll do it. We'll absolutely do it!
If it's come to this, then it's vengeance!
We're going full Kuranosuke on you!
Just Mr. Seo and me,
not 47 warriors, just two guys.
We're coming for your head, no, Merry's head!
Interesting.
So, in six months,
let's see whose head will...
Oh, a head! Hey!
That saved us an explanation, didn't it?
Mr. Seo, let's do this.
With the blade of our new character,
- we'll take this giant salamander's head!
- I am absolutely not doing it!
Not doing it?
How much more will you insult Molco?
I won't forgive you.
No matter what, I will never
forgive you, of all people!
That's right. Let's do it!
- Let's take his head!
- I am absolutely not taking his head!
We won't take it!
What? But what about vengeance?
I won't take vengeance for Molco!
Wait for me, Molco.
I won't let anyone put a stain on you.
If you run away now, won't it be
the same as when you left Merry?
Let's compete, Mr. Seo.
You don't understand anything.
It's already settled.
This match is my win by default!
Remember that.
Mr. Seo, why? Why not get vengeance?
I mentioned this before.
When I was a kid, I got teased a lot.
They told me it was weird
for a boy to like cute things.
What? That's not weird at all.
What era are you from, the Showa?
Well, but actually,
for a boy to be crazy about
cute things is pretty rare.
Kids can be cruel.
That's true.
And I used to get pretty down about it.
But Berry was always there for me.
Berry never says anything
that gives me a solid push on the back,
like encouragement or anything.
Of course, unlike Cynical Molco,
she also didn't say things
to brush people off.
She just said "Berry Good".
But with those words...
I know it's kind of late,
but I feel like I've finally figured it out.
What I like,
what I want to create. That's it.
And that's the "cute" I believe in.
Thinking about it,
maybe I should be the furthest away from
all that win-or-lose stuff from earlier.
So...
I won't let cuteness be a competition.
I will hate that giant salamander
for all eternity.
- But...
- Cuteness
won't be a competition.
Yeah.
And, at that restaurant,
you went "Bam!" to that
giant salamander for me.
How should I put it...
I'm... just... t-t-thank...
Thank... Thank... Thank...
- Thank...
- How about we go with that?
The thing about our goal.
Free from winning or losing,
with no heavy message or weird twists.
And yet, it supports someone.
It just supports them.
Let's create a character
with that kind of concept.
Just supporting.
Let's just make what you've always loved!
As expected of me.
- What?
- It's obvious, isn't it?
You've got that
"I thought of it myself" face,
but that was pretty much all me.
- Well, you're not wrong, but...
- Brazenly taking credit.
You are really the successor of hyena-ism.
And you committed
another violation, didn't you?
[Touch the cute here, and you're fired]
Bringing out Molco without permission, huh?
Well, this time it's a special exception.
I'll forgive you if you go buy this.
[Very Popular Daitaidou Nikanaru]
It's a detergent called Daitaidou Nikanaru.
It's supposed to be good for
stains on stuffed animals too.
Well, maybe next time.
No, now, okay?
I have to get the stain out.
Now? Now?
But it's already nighttime.
And besides, I don't even know
where they sell it.
You know what?
If you're sorry, just go look for it.
And if you're not, you won't.
Now which is it?
You'll go! You're sorry! Go! Run, run!
I think I can somehow manage!
Just supporting.
Make it happen!
I'm fed up!